{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "93 + 20",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 90",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 7",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 7",
      "answer": 31
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 35",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 91",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 18",
      "answer": 21
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 34",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 21",
      "answer": 48
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 19",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 1",
      "answer": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 1",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 27",
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 20",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 74",
      "answer": 143
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 45",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 9",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 76",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 59",
      "answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 50",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 9",
      "answer": 29
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 7",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 85",
      "answer": 142
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 56",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 95",
      "answer": 185
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 31",
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 26",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 60",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 4",
      "answer": 19
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 12",
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 57",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 17",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 59",
      "answer": 155
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 91",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 11",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 56",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 53",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 6",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 58",
      "answer": 140
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 65",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 20",
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 20",
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 61",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 17",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 22",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 7",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 42",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 36",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 12",
      "answer": 25
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 26",
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 99",
      "answer": 156
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 63",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 1",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 95",
      "answer": 158
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 78",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 52",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 77",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 70",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 96",
      "answer": 165
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 64",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 91",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 37",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 65",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 29",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 25",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 3",
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 94",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 76",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 91",
      "answer": 145
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 27",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 53",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 5",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 1",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 100",
      "answer": 193
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 48",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 47",
      "answer": 102
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 30",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 81",
      "answer": 140
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 6",
      "answer": 28
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 65",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 64",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 7",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 20",
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 58",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 25",
      "answer": 46
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 48",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 88",
      "answer": 102
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 73",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 8",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 20",
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 25",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 71",
      "answer": 157
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 34",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 88",
      "answer": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 50",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 50",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 72",
      "answer": 155
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 19",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 23",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 6",
      "answer": 90
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 2,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 100,
      "to": 200
    }
  }
}